前情提要
黑客軍團
進去了
ZiMuZu
傾情奉獻
小酸奶!   黑衣章魚X
翻譯
showeryhe   機器草
黑客軍團
第一季 第三集
Kallen
時間軸
Justin_R
寶寶
時間軸&后期&特效
校對
黑衣草
總監
草society
我將會成為這家公司有史以來最年輕的高管
I will be the youngest executive this company has ever seen.
那好  我買了
All right, you know, I'll take it,
你能別纏著我們嗎
if you leave us alone.
-謝謝您  -那好
- Thank you. - All right.
聽聽第二首
Check track two out.
-第二首  -回見  哥們
- Track two. - All right, man.
你為什么沒告訴我dat文件的事
Why didn't you tell me about the dat file?
一輩子都在邪惡公司工作
Worked at Evil Corp his whole life.
突然就被解雇了
And out of the blue, he got fired.
沒人知道原因
No one knew why.
他得了白血病
He had leukemia.
還逼我不可以告訴別人
Made me swear to never tell anyone,
最后  我太擔心了  就告訴了我媽
Finally, I got so worried told my mom.
他知道后  大為光火
When he found out, he got pissed.
你想過或許你是活該嗎
You ever think you deserved it?
我才8歲
I was eight years ol--
你沒有遵守你們的神圣約定
You didn't commit to the sacred pact you'd formed.
我對本公司未來業務發展的規劃
My approach within our business units
就是優先投資研發前沿技術
is to first invest in new technologies
并盡早投入使用
and develop prototypes
以此把握科技界的最新潮流
in order to understand the technology potential,
因為盡管我公司網絡安全部門
because despite the recent success
最近所取得的成功
of our cyber security team,
但眼下仍然有
our company currently still has
多達72個可被侵入的安全漏洞
72 potential hacker vulnerabilities
威脅著我司的主數據...
in our primary and secon--
慢著  是73個  你個蠢貨
oh, wait. It's 73, you stupid piece of shit.
再來
Again.
眼下仍然有
Our company currently still has
多達73個可被侵入的安全漏洞
73 potential hacker vulnerabilities
威脅著我司的主數據中心和副數據中心
in our primary and secondary data centers.
現在我們絕對不能
Now is not the time to be encumbered
受累于痛失首席技術官的
by the company's tragic and shameful loss
悲劇性事件之...
of our chief te--
太他媽正式了
Too formal, God damn it.
語氣溫和點  別跟個機器人似的
Warm it up. Don't be a cold robot.
再來
Again.
現在我們絕對不能
Now is not the time to be encumbered
受累于痛失首席技術官的
by the company's tragic and shameful loss
悲劇性事件
of our chief technology officer.
我們必須盡快指定新的首席技術官
We have to be swift in naming the replacement CTO,
那么  各位先生  請允許我毛遂自薦
and, sir, I would like to suggest it be me.
為了我公司更光明的未來
For the sake of our company,
我們今天必須明智決定
that we make our decision today,
我的晉升
my promotion--
我的內部晉升不僅彰顯了我公司堅定的信心
My internal promotion shows not only our confidence as a company,
更向公眾展示了我們的無畏
but strength in our boldness to the public.
多謝各位撥冗
Thank you for your time.
新任首席技術官就是你
You will be the next CTO of this company.
您真的不需要什么嗎
Sure you don't want anything?
果汁  茶什么的
Pellegrino, tea?
先生  非常感謝您見我
Sir, thank you again for seeing me.
提利爾  恐怕我們得重新安排了
Tyrell, I'm gonna have to reschedule this.
-安瓦  重排下日程  -先生  我覺得...
- Anwar, set up another time. - Sir, it's just that I think--
我明白  我明白
I get it, I get it.
我們馬上就再給你安排個時間
We'll get another meeting on the books right away.
我們找到了一個非常優秀的首席技術官人選
We've got a really good CTO candidate
董事會非常青睞這個人
the board is very excited about.
不過他們還沒定下來
They're not ready to discuss it yet.
我們會給你安排好的
We'll loop you in.
讓我們考慮幾周  可以嗎
Just give us a couple of weeks, hmm?
給威利克重新排個時間
Uh, put Wellick back on the books.
就等兩周
Two weeks.
領帶不錯啊
Oh, nice tie.
我猜猜
Let me guess.
布里奧尼的
Brioni?
品味總是這么好
Great taste, as always.
回見
Be well.
我這就把具體細節發給您的助手
I'll email your assistant the details.
如果不麻煩的話
If you could,
直接發給我吧
just email it to me directly.
這事對我太重要  不容有失
This is too important for me to miss.
威利克先生  我們到了
Mr. Wellick, we're here.
這次能給我300塊錢嗎
You think I could have 300 this time?
還真像個資本主義者
Spoken like a true capitalist.
工作不順嗎
Bad day at the office?
看來真的
No ki--
求你了  別打了  停
Please, enough. No more.
大多數程序員都認為軟件除漏
Most coders think debugging software
就是修正錯誤
is about fixing a mistake,
不過這是胡扯
but that's bullshit.
除漏的關鍵其實是找到錯漏
Debugging's actually all about finding the bug,
理解這個漏洞從何而來
about understanding why the bug was there to begin with,
以及明白漏洞的出現并非偶然
about knowing that its existence was no accident.
漏洞向你傳達了信息
It came to you to deliver a message,
就像一個毫無意識的氣泡浮出水面
like an unconscious bubble floating to the surface,
爆出你可能早就心知肚明的真相
popping with a revelation you've secretly known all along.
我不知道我為什么說這些
I don't know why I'm saying all of this.
也許是因為打了太多禮來制藥
Maybe it's because I'm pumped up on whatever---
用來圈錢的  不知道什么合法藥品
legal drug dealers like Eli Lilly make money off nowadays.
不過一般是因為我預見到了
But usually it's because there's a sense it's coming.
正有只蟲子[漏洞]朝我飛來
A bug buzzing its way towards me
攪得我不得安寧  逼我作出決定
to gum up the works until it forces me to make a call.
殺了我還是接受我
Kill me or embrace me.
又或者我只是有點嚇著了  因為我沒想到
Or maybe I'm just freaking out because I never thought
會醒來看到這兩個女人盯著我
I'd wake up to find these two women staring back at me.
你醒了嗎
Are you awake?
我說不清
I don't know.
你怎么來了
What are you doing here?
我幾個小時前剛來時  你我還說過話呢
We talked maybe a few hours ago when I first got here.
你忘了嗎
You don't remember?
他們說我是你的緊急聯絡人
They said I was your emergency contact.
對了  你還要他們聯系你的心理醫生
Right. Um, you told them to call your psychiatrist.
只有咨詢了心理醫生之后你才能出院
You can't leave until you talk to one.
我出去等著了
So I'm gonna wait outside.
你還記得你向醫務人員點名聯系我嗎
Do you remember requesting me from the staff?
你要我來是因為警察說
You requested me because the police said that--
我被幾個小青年偷襲了
I got jumped by a bunch of kids.
沒什么大不了的
It's not the end of the world.
他們要做全面的藥檢  你拒絕了
They wanted to do a full drug panel, and you refused.
我能問問原因嗎
May I ask why?
艾略特  如果我們都不能好好談談的話
Elliot, if we can't have a conversation about this...
我一直在用嗎啡
I've been taking morphine.
為什么
Why?
我也沒什么合理的理由給你
I don't have a good enough reason to give you.
我希望有  但我沒有
I wish I did, but I don't.
也許你應該去戒毒
Maybe we should consider rehab.
我不是癮君子
I'm not a junkie.
那你得證明給我看
Then you'll need to prove it to me.
每兩個月自愿參加一次藥檢
Submit to a bimonthly drug test voluntarily.
只有這樣我才會同意你出院
That's the only way that I'll recommend your release.
醫院
Hospitals.
像這樣高度聯網的機構
A heavily networked one like this
黑進去太輕松了
are almost too easy to hack.
這位是威廉·海斯密斯
This is William Highsmith.
他不止是這家醫院技術部門的頭頭
He's not only the head of the IT department here,
他還是整個部門唯一的員工
he is the IT department.
他還是個白癡
He's also an idiot,
但我倒不怨他  因為雇用他的人
not that I blame him because the people that hired him
也是一群白癡
are also idiots.
這可憐鬼每年只有7000塊左右的預算
The poor guy only gets a budget of about 7,000 bucks a year,
就憑他還想保護自家網絡
and he's supposed to protect their network
不被我這樣的人黑
from people like me?
一點機會都沒有
He never stood a chance.
他用Windows98系統上沒用的
He uses useless virus scans, dated servers,
病毒掃描軟件  過時服務器和安全軟件
and security software that runs on Windows 98.
我就是因為這一點  才指定這家醫院
It's one of the reasons why I made this place
為我的優先收治醫院
my primary care facility.
藥品檢測  陽性
我可以把我的病歷
I can make my health records
改得就像那些順從的活死人一樣正常
look like every other obedient zombie out there.
陰性
好
Okay.
你不用擔心
You don't have to worry.
我不會再嗑嗎啡了
I'm not gonna do morphine again.
你這兒有火柴嗎
Hey, you got some matches?
多謝
Thank you.
能量飲料  無糖  低卡
你這早餐真簡單
That's a nice breakfast.
抱歉  信用卡刷不了
Sorry. Credit card system is down.
由于邪惡公司最近的入侵事故  本店信用卡系統無法使用
如我所說
Like I said,
除漏最難的一點
the most difficult thing about debugging
不是修補漏洞
isn't fixing the bug.
大規模黑客攻擊
而是找到漏洞
It's all about finding the bug.
對于邪惡公司
For Evil Corp,
機器人先生通過我找到了他們的漏洞
Mr. Robot found their bug in me.
我就是那個觸發了這一切的錯漏
I was the mistake that led to all of this.
有件事我得問問你
I have to ask you one thing.
維拉被抓和你有關系嗎
Did you have something to do with Vera getting busted?
見鬼  艾略特
Shit, Elliot.
你說了你不會插手的
You said you weren't gonna do anything.
他被控殺人罪了  你知道嗎
He's on murder charges, do you know that?
他手下的人都完蛋了
His whole crew bounced.
我現在也不知道去哪掙錢了
I mean, I don't know what I'm gonna do for money now.
告訴我吧  艾略特
Just tell me, Elliot,
別撒謊
and don't lie.
你是不是做了什么
Did you do something?
沒有
No.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
發生了這么多事
I mean, with everything that happened--
我很好
I'm fine.
你的門怎么了
What happened to your door?
你不該在這里的
You're not supposed to be here, okay?
我換鎖是有原因的
I changed the locks for a reason.
玩具挺有意思
Interesting toy,
不過你還是得多花點心思
but you may want to spend a little more scratch
才能指望這玩意兒
if you actually want it to, you know,
鎖得住
work.
看這個
Check it.
絕不退縮
杰西卡·阿爾芭說她想加入去社會
Jessica Alba says she wants to join fsociety.
老天  你的臉怎么了
Jesus, what happened to your face?
怎么回事
What's going on?
我也不算什么社交禮儀公主
Well, I am not the princess of social graces,
但一般情況下都會說
but typically it goes something like,
-"你好  這位是達琳"  -別說了
- "Hi, this is Darlene." - Stop.
你該走了
You need to leave.
寶貝  說真的  我們還要討論很多事
Babe, seriously, we have a lot of shit to discuss,
所以如果你不介意...
so if you wouldn't mind...
出去
Get out.
我建議你鎮靜下來
I suggest you get a grip.
她在說什么
What was she talking about?
我得去工作了
I got to get to work.
工作  你在開玩笑嗎
Work? Are you serious?
你現在不能去工作  你應該請病假
You can't go to work. You have to call in sick.
我必須得去
I have to go.
絕不退縮
漏洞不僅僅是個錯誤
A bug is never just a mistake.
這說明有更大的問題
It represents something bigger.
思想上的紕漏
An error of thinking.
-先生  先生  先生  -這說明你是怎樣的人
- Sir! Sir! Sir! - That makes you who you are.
先生  你錢包掉了
Sir! You dropped your wallet.
-謝謝  -站住
- Thanks. - Stop!
站住  他偷了我的錢包
Stop! He stole my purse.
那是你的錢包嗎
That was your wallet?
是啊  你給他的那個是我的錢包
Yes, that was my wallet you just gave him.
站住
Stop!
你是我們的  你得乖乖聽我們的話
他黑進了我的系統
He got into my system,
他要我在工作電腦上播放這張CD
and he wants me to put the CD on one of the computers at work.
你是我們的  你得乖乖聽我們的話
-他為什么要這么做  -我不知道  斯黛拉
- Why does he want to do that? - I don't know, Stella.
他沒有跟我解釋清楚
He didn't give me a full explanation.
那么他有我的裸照嘍
So he's got naked pics of me?
我們說了這么多  你就只關心
Is that the only thing you're seriously taking away
這件事嗎
from this conversation?
寶貝
Hey, babe.
跑得怎么樣
How was your run?
怪怪的
Strange.
有人掉了錢包
Someone dropped their wallet,
我撿起來還給他  然后有個...
and I picked it up to give it to them, but then this--
這有什么好奇怪的
Nothing strange about that--
只說明你的心地多么善良
just shows how good of a person you are.
一向如此
Always have been.
幾乎都有點過分了
Almost to a fault.
什么意思
What does that mean?
只是想說...
Just that you--
你對于這個世界來說太善良了
you're too good for the world.
也許這就是我愛你的原因吧
That's probably why I love you.
我要去沖個澡
I'm gonna hop in the shower.
我說了我不方便說話
I told you I can't talk.
你有100小時時間
You have 100 hours precisely.
之后  我們就會公布手上的一切
After that, everything we own will be released.
他很快就會崩潰
單把注意力集中在記錄上還不夠
It's not enough just to focus your attention on the logs.
我們還得時刻關注社交媒體的動向
We should also monitor social media traffic
比如實時聊天  文檔共享平臺
as well as IRC, Pastebin.
設置一個全天候運行的腳本
And set up scripts to keep going 24/7.
我們說不定會撞大運
I mean, we might get lucky.
他們一松懈就會犯錯...
They might get sloppy, make a mistake, you know...
我們就生活在這種世界里
This is the world we live in.
人們利用他人犯下的錯誤
People relying on each other's mistakes
來操控別人  甚至互相利用
to manipulate one another and use one another,
與人產生聯系
even relate to one another.
溫馨又混亂的人性圈
A warm, messy circle of humanity.
艾略特
Elliot.
我請你們今晚來我家吃晚飯
I'm inviting you guys to dinner tonight.
雖然不如莫爾頓牛排坊  但我做的也不差
Morton's notwithstanding, I cook a mean steak.
怎么了  老板就不能請自己最喜歡的員工吃晚飯嗎
What? Can't a boss invite his favorite employees to dinner?
不  沒關系  但我有安排了
No, that's cool, but I got plans.
能讓我倆單獨談談嗎
Can you guys give us a minute?
好的
Yeah.
你準備告訴我發生了什么嗎
You want to tell me what's going on?
還是不了
Not really.
你翹班  然后這個樣子出現
You're missing work, you come in looking like that,
還指望我不問嗎
and you expect me not to ask questions?
我不知道你是否希望我關心
Look, I don't know how much you want me asking
你的個人生活  但是
about your personal life, but--
其實完全不希望
Not at all, actually.
我無意冒犯
I mean, I don't mean to be rude.
我只是實話實說
I was-- I'm just being honest.
機器人先生可能發現了邪惡公司的漏洞
Mr. Robot may have found Evil Corp's bug,
但他沒發現我的
but he didn't find mine.
只有這樣才能保護我自己
That's the only way to protect myself.
絕對不能給他們看我的源代碼
Never show them my source code.
封閉自己
Close myself off.
創造出冰冷的完美迷宮
Create my cold, perfect maze
沒人能找到我
where no one can ever find me.
艾略特  真不敢相信你在這兒工作
Elliot, I cannot believe you work here.
這地方好破
This place is a shithole.
我想來看看你  然后一起吃午飯
Look, I thought I'd swing by, take you to lunch.
身材真好
Oh, that's nice.
她好像喜歡你  兄弟
I think she likes you, bud.
好吧  叫上她
All right, fine, I'll take her,
不過記住了  我在努力做個好助攻
but let the record show I was trying to be a good wingman.
冷靜點  真是的
Oh, calm down. Shit.
反正我也不怎么喜歡紅發妹
I'm not that into redheads anyway.
愛爾蘭這個國家總讓我萎得不行
The whole nation of Ireland makes my dick soft.
滾
Leave.
達琳說我們該談談
Darlene said we need to talk.
馬上滾蛋
Leave now.
沒錯  或許是不該在這兒談
You're right. Probably shouldn't talk here.
去隔壁的酒吧
Let's go to that bar next door.
我不會跟你去任何地方
I'm not going anywhere with you.
除非你跟我走  否則我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere until you do,
要么我們在這兒鬧開
so I can hang out here and create a scene,
要么我們到隔壁酒吧談5分鐘
or you can give me five minutes at the bar next door.
不管哪種情況  我都會很開心
Either way, I'm gonna have fun.
任君選擇
Dealer's choice.
怎么了  這是蘋果馬提尼
What? It's an appletini.
我真該踹死你
I should kick your ass.
如果那就算扯平了  隨你
If that'll make us square, you have my blessing.
伙計  我才不想動你
Nah, man, I want nothing to do with you.
你就是個瘋子
You're a maniac.
你要什么
What can I get for you?
什么都不要
Uh, nothing.
你應該點些飲料
You should probably order something.
-我推薦這個...  -好吧
- I'd recommend this... - Fine.
我要一杯蘋果馬提尼
I'll--I'll have an appletini.
這算是夸你  伙計
You should take it as a compliment, guy.
這酒太他媽好喝了
These things are goddamn delicious.
我懂  贊美也讓我不舒服
I get it. Compliments make me uncomfortable too.
我覺得很難相信
I find that hard to believe.
對啊  我騙誰呢  我愛贊美
Yeah, who am I kidding? I love compliments.
12美元
$12.
我認為你沒有好好品
I really don't think you enjoyed that.
-建議你抿著喝  -最后問你一次
- I suggest sipping-- - Last chance.
你想要什么
What do you want?
我為自己的行為抱歉
I'm sorry for what I did.
我才不買賬
I don't buy it.
更重要的是  我也不在乎
More importantly, I don't give a shit.
我沒想傷害你
I never wanted to hurt you.
暴力的人所以暴力
People who get violent get that way
是因為不知道怎么交流
because they can't communicate.
你爸爸
Your dad,
我相信他那么做自己也不好受
I bet he felt shitty for doing what he did.
他肯定也想道歉
I'm sure he wanted to apologize too.
有時把孩子推開更容易
Sometimes pushing your kid away is just easier.
別老是生他的氣了  孩子
Don't stay mad at him too long, kiddo.
你要走嗎
You're leaving?
如你所愿  對吧
That's what you want, isn't it?
那你的計劃呢
What about your plan?
計劃
Plan?
你是整件事的關鍵
You're the key to the whole thing.
沒了你  計劃也不存在了
Without you, there is no plan.
就這樣
That's it?
都結束了
It's over?
你指望我信嗎
Expect me to believe that?
下輩子再見
See you in another life.
聽到了嗎
Did you hear that?
難以置信
I can't believe it.
真的發生了嗎
Is it really happening?
去社會終于結束了
Fsociety finally over.
我花了幾年時間創造出的現實世界
The recent glitch in the otherwise neat reality
除最近這個故障外一切都好
I created over the years.
我再也不會像那樣出岔子了
I'll never slip up like that again.
我現在要變得更正常
I'm gonna be more normal now.
也許夏拉甚至可以做我的女友
Maybe Shayla could even be my girlfriend.
我可以和她一起去看那些傻逼漫威電影
I'll go see those stupid Marvel movies with her.
去健身房鍛煉
I'll join a gym.
在圖片分享上點贊
I'll heart things on Instagram.
喝香草拿鐵
I'll drink vanilla lattes.
從現在開始過上沒有漏洞的生活
I'm gonna lead a bug-free life from now on.
為保護我的完美迷宮不惜一切
Anything to protect my perfect maze.
吉迪恩
Hey, Gideon.
今晚那個晚宴還舉行嗎
Is that dinner still on for tonight?
是的  當然
Um, yeah. Sure.
你想來嗎
Uh, you want to come?
是啊
Yeah.
很好
Great.
我能帶上女友嗎
Can I bring my girlfriend?
你有女朋友啊
You have a girlfriend?
還沒問過呢
Well, I, uh, haven't asked her yet,
但我會的
but I will.
希望她能答應
Hopefully she'll say yes.
可以  當然
Uh, yeah. Sure.
太好了
Perfect.
謝謝
Thanks.
他是在喝星巴克嗎
Was he drinking Starbucks?
你還沒把CD播出來啊
Are you still trying to rip that CD?
嗯  都劃壞了
Yeah, it's all-- it's all scratched up.
我們走吧
Let's get out of here.
安瓦·拉齊茲  執行總裁菲利普·普萊斯個人助理
飛吻俱樂部
飛吻俱樂部  打開地圖
你要去哪
飛吻俱樂部
你為什么要去那兒
工作
你非去不可嗎
我做的一切都是為我們
我們
還是你
就是我
別睡太晚
我老板邀請我今晚去他家赴晚宴
My boss invited me to a dinner party at his place tonight.
你愿不愿作為我的女朋友跟我一起去
I thought you could come as my girlfriend.
什么
What?
你真是正在要我做你女朋友嗎
Are you actually asking me to be your girlfriend right now?
對
Yeah.
總之  我需要你
Anyway, I need you.
我不擅長處理這種社交場合
I'm not good in social situations like that.
你真的很有毛病
There is something seriously wrong with you.
我不要再被你利用了
I'm not gonna be used anymore.
你怎么不約今早那個女孩
Why don't you ask the girl from this morning, okay?
她看上去像是愿意跟你去什么
She seems like she might want to go to some stupid,
無聊的破晚宴
stuffy dinner party.
你并不了解我
You don't actually know me.
你只知道我是...
All you know is that I'm the girl...
我當然了解夏拉
Of course I know Shayla.
請升級您的賬戶設置
她一搬進隔壁我就黑了她的電郵
I hacked her email as soon as she moved in next door.
今天就升級您的賬戶
密碼  現在密碼  新密碼  再次輸入
只靠一個簡單的網絡釣魚
With a simple phishing scam,
我就輕松拿到了她的密碼
I owned her password pretty easily.
我不是說你能在網上找到的那些
I'm not talking about the stuff you can find online.
我說的是真實的我
I'm talking about the real me.
那就告訴我吧
Tell me, then.
不  算了
No. Forget it.
我想知道
I want to know.
這是什么
What is this?
我就是把一些元素拼湊在了
I just put all the elements...
-好美  -一起
- It's beautiful. - Together.
這我從沒見過
I've never seen this before.
-她肯定...  -從沒發到網上
- She must-- - Never posted online.
很多都...
Um, I mean, a lot of them's not--
沒完成呢
they're not done.
她也有自己的私人迷宮
She's got her own private maze too.
用了很多不同的部分
Took a lot of different pieces,
從不同的東西上取來的
um, from different things,
我的照片  畫什么的
like from my photographs or drawings and--
看這個
Like, there's this one.
挺老套的
Um, it's really f---ing corny,
但上面什么都有  孩子什么的
but, like, it has everything-- the kids and the...
夏拉的漏洞我一直捉摸不透
Shayla's bug was always elusive to me.
或許就是這個
Maybe this was it.
渴望正常  卻卡在邊緣
Wanting normalcy but stuck in the outer fringes,
不知該如何參與進去
not knowing how to participate.
就像我一樣
Just like me.
我能吻你嗎
Can I kiss you?
下次別問了
Next time, don't ask.
太傻了
It's lame.
漏洞一向名聲不好
Bugs usually get a bad rap.
但有時候
But sometimes...
別讓我失望  好嗎
Don't let me down, okay?
當一個漏洞終于顯現
When a bug finally makes itself known,
也會讓人興奮
it can be exhilarating,
就像你剛剛解鎖了什么
like you just unlocked something.
一個美好的機會
A grand opportunity
就等著你去利用
waiting to be taken advantage of.
威利克先生
Mr. Wellick?
你叫什么來著
What was your name again?
安瓦
Anwar.
我不知道你也來這種地方
I didn't know you came to places like this.
我不來
I don't.
什么意思  你不是來了嗎
What do you mean? You're here now.
我來是因為你
I'm here because you are.
什么  抱歉  我不懂
What? Sorry, I don't get it.
我覺得你很美  我想帶你回家
I think you're beautiful. I want to take you home.
等等  你不是結婚了嗎
Wait, I thought you were married.
因為  畢竟  漏洞唯一的作用
Because, after all, a bug's only purpose,
它存在的唯一原因
its only reason for existence
就是作為等待修補的錯誤
is to be a mistake that needs fixing,
幫你糾正錯誤
to help you right a wrong.
有什么比這感覺更棒的呢
And what feels better than that?
艾略特
So, Elliot,
你不介紹一下嗎
do you think you should introduce us?
夏拉  這是安吉拉和奧利
Oh, um, Shayla, this is Angela and Ollie.
你今晚很美
You, uh, you look lovely this evening.
好啊  伙計們
What up, guys?
你們才到嗎
You just get here?
西裝不錯
Nice suit.
謝了  伙計
Thanks, dude.
-該死  -你是怎么了
- Shit. - What is up with you?
你這一晚上都煩躁不安的
You've been fidgeting all night.
我們再按一次門鈴吧
Maybe we should try the doorbell again.
你們好啊
Hey, guys.
你們站多久了
How long have you been standing out here?
門鈴壞了  我該說一聲的
The doorbell is broken. I should have warned you.
請進吧  我是哈利
Come in. I'm Harry, by the way.
-安吉拉  認識你很高興  -認識你很高興
- Angela. Nice to meet you. - Good to meet you.
很高興終于能對上
Always nice to put a face...
員工號和臉了
with an employee badge number, right?
奧利  你們在一起多久了
Ollie, how long have you guys been together?
-兩年半  -兩年
- 2 1/2 years. - 2 years.
好吧
Okay.
艾略特  你和夏拉在一起多久了
Elliot, how long have you and Shayla been together?
這個
Well, uh, um,
就今天才開始
j-just today.
好了  你審夠客人了吧
Okay, enough grilling of the guests.
我們去看看烤爐吧
Let's check on the real grill, shall we?
艾略特  幫幫忙
Elliot, I could use your help.
我要向你承認件事
So I have a confession.
我讓杜勒斯數據中心的系統管理員
I had the sys admins at the data center in Dulles
又去看了一遍那個服務器
check that server again.
吉迪恩  你做了什么
Gideon, what did you do?
當然了  根本沒找到什么
Of course there was nothing.
我真不知道我為什么要起疑
I have no idea what there was to even be suspicious about.
你會有什么動機
I mean, what possible motivation would you have
去搞破壞  我大概只是...
to do anything? I guess I was just being--
吉迪恩必須放手
Gideon has to let this go.
如果他靠近這個馬蜂窩
If he comes near this hornet's nest,
我不知道我是不是能救下他
I'm not sure I can save him from it.
我得消除他任何的疑慮
I have to kill any suspicion left.
你在眾安一直努力工作
You've been nothing but a hard worker for Allsafe,
所以  我道歉
so I apologize.
我們在飛機上聊過之后
After the conversation on the plane,
我認識到這關系到整個公司的命運
I knew what was at stake-- the whole company.
我擔心我找到的dat文件并不是要緊的那個
I was worried that the dat file I found wasn't the right one.
我就是不想...
I just didn't
讓你抱有希望  以免是我錯了
want to get your hopes up in case I was wrong.
所以會面之前我并沒跟你說
That's why I didn't tell you before the meeting.
該死
Shit.
我得讓他抱我了  是嗎
I'm gonna have to let him hug me, aren't I?
你真是個優秀的工程師  艾略特
You're such a brilliant engineer, Elliot,
你絕對不要懷疑自己的才華
and you should never doubt your skills
不管我給了你多大壓力
no matter how much pressure I put on you.
而且你更不用對我有所隱瞞
And you certainly don't have to keep anything from me.
我關心你
I care about you.
《巴茲爾弗蘭維勒太太的混亂檔案》
From the Mixed-up Files of Basil E. Frankweiler.
我就是受了那個的啟發  記得嗎
That's where I got the idea, remember?
我是那么想做克勞迪婭·金凱德[書中人物]
I wanted to be Claudia Kincaid so bad.
就連她的名字都那么酷
Even her name was cool.
記得嗎  我們以為我們是去的大都會博物館
Remember we thought we were going to the Met,
結果不知卻怎么跑到了皇后區博物館
somehow we ended up at the Queens Museum instead?
當時可沒有谷歌地圖
No Google Maps back then.
我喜歡跟你離家出走
I loved running away with you.
八歲的時候
Somehow when you're eight,
離家出走還挺好玩的
running away can be fun.
正常生活
The normal life.
說說笑笑  赴晚宴
Smiles, dinner parties,
童年回憶
childhood stories.
我可以習慣這樣的生活
I could get used to this,
甚至喜歡上它
maybe even like it.
怎么了
What's wrong?
...入侵丑聞仍在繼續
Corp's hacking scandal continues
現在又有大量電郵被放出
with the release of these latest emails.
首席技術官泰瑞·科比涉嫌與93年泄露事件有關  邪惡公司遭竊數據顯示重大掩蓋事件
根據最新遭披露的資料顯示
Information stemming from the latest dump reveals
泰瑞·科比與另外兩位高管
that Terry Colby was one of three high-level executives
共同參與了掩蓋廣為人知的
involved in the cover-up of the widely publicized
華盛頓鎮有毒廢料丑聞
Washington Township toxic waste scandal.
有毒廢料丑聞
如果這些報道屬實
If these reports are true,
科比可能將面臨更多指控
Colby may be facing more indictments.
1993年曾有傳聞
In the ensuing 24 months
稱發生有毒廢料泄露事件  隨后兩年中
after the alleged toxic waste leak in 1993,
有26名員工死于類型相似的白血病
26 employees died from similar types of leukemia.
然而邪惡公司卻得以駁回了幸存受害者
Evil Corp, however, managed to get the class-action lawsuit
提出的集體訴訟
filed against it by the surviving victims dismissed,
聲稱并無證據能表明
claiming there was no direct evidence linking
其工廠與確診病例有關
their factories to the diagnoses.
而如今泄露的郵件表明科比實際上
Now these emails indicate that Colby was in fact
了解毒物的危險程度
aware of the dangerous levels of toxicity
卻依然對此保密  因為
and kept it a secret as it
"即使可能面臨訴訟  重組現有
"Would not be cost-effective to retool the current systems
系統仍是得不償失"
in place even if there are potential lawsuits."
科比先生不能對此作出回應  但其律師稱
Mr. Colby was unavailable for comment, but his lawyer...
我的完美迷宮
My perfect maze
在我眼前崩潰了
crumbling before my eyes.
數據公布進一步證明科比是遭到了陷害
Data dump are further proof Colby was set up,
但他們并未指明是誰干的
but they didn't indicate by whom.
我再無法隱藏了
There's nothing to hide behind.
我還以為不存在  但確實有的
I didn't think it existed, but there it was.
現在有了
Is.
機器人先生終于找到了我的漏洞
Mr. Robot finally found my bug.
...將華盛頓鎮廢料量
Linking the waste levels in Washington Township
與受害者疾病關聯起來
to the victims' illnesses.
法律分析員支持這一說法
Legal analysts support the claim
的確沒有足夠證據證明...
that there is not enough evidence...
怎么回事
What's going on?
我媽媽和艾略特的爸爸就是這么...
That's how my mom, um, and Elliot's dad--
-我得走了  -等等
- I have to go. - Wait, wait.
-我跟你一起走吧  -不  還是別了
- Let me come with you. - No, I'd rather you didn't.
...華盛頓鎮丑聞證據
Evidence in the Washington Township scandal.
泰瑞·科比仍在接受調查
Terry Colby remains under investigation
關于其在這件事中的...
for his alleged involvement with the...
...駁回...并無證據能
Dismissed because there was no evidence
將華盛頓鎮廢料量...
linking the waste levels in Washington Township...
邪惡公司
Evil Corp...
別那么苦著臉
Don't look so sad.
他是自己作死
He did this to himself.
他放棄了  他是個懦夫
He gave in. He was a coward.
他軟弱  可悲
He was weak and pathetic.
說到底  這才是害死你父親的
And in the end, that's what killed your father.
你為什么在哭
Why are you crying?
別問那么多問題
Don't ask so many questions.
我想他
I miss him.
這毫無意義
There's no point to that.
但我就是想他
But I do.
那你也跟他一樣軟弱
Then you're just as weak as him.
你不難過嗎
You're not sad?
我憑什么
Why should I be?
夜色多美
It's a beautiful night.
天氣也這么好
The weather is nice,
我在好好抽煙
and I'm enjoying my cigarette.
漏洞逼迫軟件去適應
The bug forces the software to adapt,
因其存在而進化成新的東西
evolve into something new because of it.
要么繞過它  要么撐過去
Work around it or work through it.
不管怎樣  軟件都得改變
No matter what, it changes.
變成新的東西
It becomes something new.
新版本
The next version.
不可避免的升級
The inevitable upgrade.
你真是個怪人
You're a strange creature.
我就是個生意人
I'm just a businessman.
我只能擦這么干凈了
And that's about as clean as I'm gonna get it.
你去洗澡吧
You have to do the rest in the shower.
我不介意臟一點
I don't mind being a little dirty.
我介意
I do.
安裝特權用戶
你是否想安裝此應用  允許此應用查看你的私人信息
應用安裝成功
為完成安裝  需允許監督人請求
超級用戶請求
是否隱藏超級用戶標志  是
以根模式運行
輸入上方所示密碼
正在配置
激活成功
你也來吧
You should join me.
嗯  就過去
Yeah, I'll be there in a minute.
抱歉我那樣跑掉了
I'm sorry that I ran off like that.
你跟他談了嗎
Did you talk to him?
沒有  他不在家
Nope. He wasn't home.
我在
Well, I'm here.
我樂意跟你談談
I want to talk to you about everything,
但今晚不行  好嗎
just not tonight, okay?
你愿意跟他談  卻不愿跟自己男友談嗎
So you talk to him but not your own boyfriend?
這不一樣  奧利
It's different, Ollie.
我們都有親人死于...
Both of our parents died because...
我們就是這么認識的
That's how we know each other.
我現在真不想談這個
I really don't want to talk about this right now.
如果我想呢
What if I do?
想什么
What if you do what?
想談談
Want to talk.
關于
About...
一件事
something.
你說什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?
我有事要告訴你
I have to tell you something.
我真不知道你干嗎要這么折磨自己
I don't know why you're putting yourself through this.
你不用一直翻看的
You don't have to keep looking at it.
這毫無意義
All right? It meant nothing.
我知道這話我說好多遍了
Okay, I know I sound like a broken record,
安吉拉·莫斯賬戶概覽
但我愛的是你  我想跟你在一起
but I love you, and I want to be with you.
別說話了
Stop speaking.
告訴我  要怎么樣
Just tell me what you need
我才能彌補  我會做的
in order for me to fix this, and I'll do it.
我們得分手
We need to break up.
安吉拉  別這樣
Angela, come on.
你還給我別的選擇了嗎  奧利
What choice did you give me, Ollie?
我知道我有問題
Look, I know I have a problem.
我不否認
I'm not denying that.
或許我的問題就是
Well, maybe my problem is
我不能跟有你這種問題的人在一起
I can't be with a guy with your problem.
CD在哪
Where's the CD?
在我包里  怎么了
It's in my-- in my bag. Why?
他掌握了我的銀行賬戶  奧利
He has my bank account, Ollie.
-還有我爸的銀行賬戶  -怎么...
- And my dad's bank account. - How did they--
因為我的學生貸款  我們的賬戶是相連的
Our accounts are linked because of my student loans.
我用你的筆記本登錄過
I used your laptop to access it.
他拿到了我爸的社保信息
He has my dad's social security,
他的信用卡密碼  所有一切
his credit card numbers, everything.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  這可不妙
Okay, that is bad,
但警察肯定能...
but I'm sure the cops will figure out a way--
如果你不照這人說的做
If we don't do what this guy says
而我們去找警察  他會把這些信息
and we go to the cops, then he's just going to sell
賣給出價最高的人
our information to the highest bidder,
我和我爸爸就完全毀了
and me and my dad are completely screwed.
你知道遭遇這樣的
Do you have any idea how difficult it is
大規模身份盜竊  要恢復過來有多難嗎
to come back from massive identity theft like this?
你什么意思
What are you saying?
安吉拉  你瘋了嗎
Angela, are you crazy?
不  我們不能為此就
No, we cannot just infect Allsafe's network
感染眾安的網絡
because of this.
我會丟了工作的
I'll lose my job.
說到點子上了
And there it is.
你也會丟工作的
You'll lose your job too,
如果你在乎的話
if that matters.
再說  即便我們照做
Besides, even if we put the CD in,
你怎么知道這人就不會還是賣掉信息呢
who says this guy won't just do all this anyway?
過來
Hey, hey, come here.
看著我
Look at me.
我們會想到辦法的
We are going to figure this out.
好嗎
Okay?
你沒事的  你不會有事的
You're right. You're right.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我就是好怕
I'm just scared.
我不想跟你分手的
I don't want to break up with you.
我不該那么說
I'm sorry that I said that.
我好愛你
I love you so much.
檢查報告
證據
華盛頓鎮有毒廢料丑聞  科比是自我證罪了嗎
這里是杜勒斯系統管理員
This is admin, Dulles.
我是眾安安全的吉迪恩·戈達德
Yeah, hi, this is Gideon Goddard at Allsafe Security.
我要再找下肖恩·斯凱勒談談CS30服務器
I need to talk to Sean Skyler about server CS30 again.
請稍等  我為您轉接
Hold please. I'll transfer you.
不是吧  非要今晚嗎
怎么不行了
我累了
我不管
要紅的
工作得如何了
還在進行中
那么說你失敗了
進行怎么就成失敗了
反正不是成功
再緊點
還有腳
她會得到工作嗎
是她丈夫  斯考特·諾爾斯
看來董事會已經審查過他了
他們下周要見面
那我們得盡快請他們來吃飯
你不覺得那樣太明顯了嗎
雖然我想  但我們似乎沒時間遮遮掩掩的了
你還沒弄完呢
你這個樣子  真的不要緊嗎
我們商量過了
就一小會兒
計劃是這樣的
Here's the plan.